linkstorms.com 2018-12-27

# 

### _Updated: January 23, 2013_

Information Collected on Website and in our Ads  
When you access our web site or interact with one of our ad units, we may record information that your browser collects. This data may include, but is not limited to, your computer’s Internet Protocol address, your geographic location (country, state, city and zip), browser type, the web page you’re currently visiting, and the web page you last were viewing. In addition, we may also use “cookies” to collect information (see below for our policies related to cookies).

Use of Info Collected  
We may use non-personally identifying information collected within our ads specifically to create a better user experience for you. This may allow us to better direct ads to you based on your preferences. It also helps us to better measure the effectiveness of our ads.

Linkstorm units may be designed to enable the collection of Personally Identifiable Information (PII) supplied voluntarily by users, such as a location (town of residence or zip code), gender, name, phone, email address, et cetera when requested by advertisers or publishers. In such cases, should you not consent to the use of your personal Information, do not supply it within the unit. Any personal information provided by a user is collected and distributed to the Advertiser, Publisher or its authorized third-party and is not used by us for any other purpose. The Advertiser or Publisher’s collection and use of the user-supplied information is defined by the Advertiser or Publisher’s privacy policy and we are not responsible for their privacy or information practices.

Additionally, within some Linkstorm units a user may submit Personally Identifiable Information about another person through such functionalities as refer-a-friend, group discounts or other such offerings. As with any Personal Information that a user supplies about himself/herself, any Personal Information supplied on behalf of another person is provided to the Advertiser, Publisher or its authorized third-party and is not used by us for any other purpose. The Advertiser or Publisher’s collection and use of the user supplied information is defined by the Advertiser or Publisher’s privacy policy and we are not responsible for their privacy or information practices.

Cookies  
A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Most browsers are set to automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to use or access some of the interactive features offered on the site. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, deleting cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Click Help in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.

You can also opt-out of receiving cookies from third party data providers by following the instructions at: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Also, because your choices are not associated with you as a particular individual, if you change computers, web browsers or cookie settings, you will need to re-implement your preferences as described above.

Changes and Updates  
From time to time we may update our Privacy Policy. We will be sure to clearly state the date of the last Privacy Policy update. You should periodically check our Privacy Policy for updates. Accessing our web site and using our ads constitutes your agreement to our Privacy Policy.
